religionfacts.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy - ReligionFacts

ReligionFacts.com does not collect any personally-identifiable information from visitors. No part of the site requires you to register or log in, and we don't use cookies.

Like all websites, our web server automatically logs basic information about our visitors, such as how many people visited, how long they stayed, what country they're from, and what site they came from to get to ours. None of this information tells us who you are.

If you give us personal information, such as your e-mail address when writing us, we won't disclose this information to anyone else nor use it to send you anything but a reply.

This privacy policy covers www.religionfacts.com only.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Article Info

Title| Privacy Policy  
---|---  
URL| www.religionfacts.com/privacy  
Short URL| [rlft.co/1879](http://rlft.co/1879)  
Published| October 3, 2013  
Updated| November 10, 2015  
MLA Citation| “Privacy Policy.” _ReligionFacts.com._ 10 Nov. 2015. Web. Accessed 19 Nov. 2016. <www.religionfacts.com/privacy>
